[(u'<doc', u'O'), (u'id="21197"', u'O'), (u'url="https:en.wikipedia.orgwiki?curid=21197"', u'O'), (u'title="Nintendo">', u'O')][(u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION')][][(u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Co.,', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Ltd.', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Japanese', u'O'), (u'multinational', u'O'), (u'consumer', u'O'), (u'electronics', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'headquartered', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Kyoto,', u'O'), (u'Japan.', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'one', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u"world's", u'O'), (u'largest', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'companies', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'market', u'O'), (u'capitalization.', u'O'), (u'Founded', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'23', u'O'), (u'September', u'O'), (u'1889', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'Fusajiro', u'O'), (u'Yamauchi,', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'originally', u'O'), (u'produced', u'O'), (u'handmade', u'O'), (u'hanafuda', u'O'), (u'playing', u'O'), (u'cards.', u'O'), (u'By', u'O'), (u'1963,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'had', u'O'), (u'tried', u'O'), (u'several', u'O'), (u'small', u'O'), (u'niche', u'O'), (u'businesses,', u'O'), (u'such', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'cab', u'O'), (u'services', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'love', u'O'), (u'hotels.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'word', u'O'), (u'"Nintendo"', u'O'), (u'can', u'O'), (u'be', u'O'), (u'roughly', u'O'), (u'translated', u'O'), (u'from', u'O'), (u'Japanese', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'English', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'"leave', u'O'), (u'luck', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'heaven".', u'O')][(u'Abandoning', u'O'), (u'previous', u'O'), (u'ventures', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'favor', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'toys', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'1960s,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'then', u'O'), (u'developed', u'O'), (u'into', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'1970s,', u'O'), (u'ultimately', u'O'), (u'becoming', u'O'), (u'one', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'most', u'O'), (u'influential', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'industry', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u"Japan's", u'O'), (u'third', u'O'), (u'most-valuable', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'market', u'O'), (u'value', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'over', u'O'), (u'$85', u'O'), (u'billion.', u'O'), (u'From', u'O'), (u'1992', u'O'), (u'until', u'O'), (u'2016,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'also', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'majority', u'O'), (u'shareholder', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Major', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'League', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u"Baseball's", u'O'), (u'Seattle', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Mariners.', u'ORGANIZATION')][(u',', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'has', u'O'), (u'cumulative', u'O'), (u'sales', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'over', u'O'), (u'670.43', u'O'), (u'million', u'O'), (u'hardware', u'O'), (u'units', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'4.23', u'O'), (u'billion', u'O'), (u'software', u'O'), (u'units.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'has', u'O'), (u'created', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'some', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'best-known', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'top-selling', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'franchises,', u'O'), (u'such', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'"Mario",', u'O'), (u'"The', u'O'), (u'Legend', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Zelda",', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'"Pok\xe9mon".', u'O')][(u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'founded', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'card', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'late', u'O'), (u'1889', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'Fusajiro', u'PERSON'), (u'Yamauchi.', u'O'), (u'Based', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Kyoto,', u'O'), (u'Japan,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'business', u'O'), (u'produced', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'marketed', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'playing', u'O'), (u'card', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'called', u'O'), (u'"Hanafuda".', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'handmade', u'O'), (u'cards', u'O'), (u'soon', u'O'), (u'became', u'O'), (u'popular,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Yamauchi', u'PERSON'), (u'hired', u'O'), (u'assistants', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'mass-produce', u'O'), (u'cards', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'satisfy', u'O'), (u'demand.', u'O'), (u'In', u'O'), (u'1949,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'adopted', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'name', u'O'), (u',', u'O'), (u'doing', u'O'), (u'business', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Playing', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Card', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Co.', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'outside', u'O'), (u'Japan.', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'continues', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'manufacture', u'O'), (u'playing', u'O'), (u'cards', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Japan', u'LOCATION'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'organizes', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'own', u'O'), (u'contract', u'O'), (u'bridge', u'O'), (u'tournament', u'O'), (u'called', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'"Nintendo', u'O'), (u'Cup".', u'O')][(u'In', u'O'), (u'1956,', u'O'), (u'Hiroshi', u'PERSON'), (u'Yamauchi,', u'O'), (u'grandson', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Fusajiro', u'O'), (u'Yamauchi,', u'O'), (u'visited', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'U.S.', u'LOCATION'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'talk', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'United', u'LOCATION'), (u'States', u'LOCATION'), (u'Playing', u'O'), (u'Card', u'O'), (u'Company,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'dominant', u'O'), (u'playing', u'O'), (u'card', u'O'), (u'manufacturer', u'O'), (u'there.', u'O'), (u'He', u'O'), (u'found', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'biggest', u'O'), (u'playing', u'O'), (u'card', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'world', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'using', u'O'), (u'only', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'small', u'O'), (u'office.', u'O'), (u"Yamauchi's", u'O'), (u'realization', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'playing', u'O'), (u'card', u'O'), (u'business', u'O'), (u'had', u'O'), (u'limited', u'O'), (u'potential', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'turning', u'O'), (u'point.', u'O'), (u'He', u'O'), (u'then', u'O'), (u'acquired', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'license', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'use', u'O'), (u'Disney', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'characters', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'playing', u'O'), (u'cards', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'drive', u'O'), (u'sales.', u'O')][(u'In', u'O'), (u'1963,', u'O'), (u'Yamauchi', u'PERSON'), (u'renamed', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Playing', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Card', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Co.', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Ltd.', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Co.,', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Ltd.', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'then', u'O'), (u'began', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'experiment', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'other', u'O'), (u'areas', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'business', u'O'), (u'using', u'O'), (u'newly', u'O'), (u'injected', u'O'), (u'capital', u'O'), (u'during', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'period', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'time', u'O'), (u'between', u'O'), (u'1963', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'1968.', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'set', u'O'), (u'up', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'taxi', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'called', u'O'), (u'"Daiya".', u'O'), (u'This', u'O'), (u'business', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'initially', u'O'), (u'successful.', u'O'), (u'However,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'forced', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'sell', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'because', u'O'), (u'problems', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'labour', u'O'), (u'unions', u'O'), (u'were', u'O'), (u'making', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'too', u'O'), (u'expensive', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'run', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'service.', u'O'), (u'It', u'O'), (u'also', u'O'), (u'set', u'O'), (u'up', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'love', u'O'), (u'hotel', u'O'), (u'chain,', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'TV', u'O'), (u'network,', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'food', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'(selling', u'O'), (u'instant', u'O'), (u'rice)', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'several', u'O'), (u'other', u'O'), (u'ventures.', u'O'), (u'All', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'these', u'O'), (u'ventures', u'O'), (u'eventually', u'O'), (u'failed,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'after', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'1964', u'O'), (u'Tokyo', u'LOCATION'), (u'Olympics,', u'O'), (u'playing', u'O'), (u'card', u'O'), (u'sales', u'O'), (u'dropped,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u"Nintendo's", u'O'), (u'stock', u'O'), (u'price', u'O'), (u'plummeted', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'lowest', u'O'), (u'recorded', u'O'), (u'level', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'\xa560.', u'O')][(u'In', u'O'), (u'1966,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'moved', u'O'), (u'into', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Japanese', u'O'), (u'toy', u'O'), (u'industry', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Ultra', u'O'), (u'Hand,', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'extendable', u'O'), (u'arm', u'O'), (u'developed', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'maintenance', u'O'), (u'engineer', u'O'), (u'Gunpei', u'PERSON'), (u'Yokoi', u'PERSON'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'his', u'O'), (u'free', u'O'), (u'time.', u'O'), (u'Yokoi', u'PERSON'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'moved', u'O'), (u'from', u'O'), (u'maintenance', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'new', u'O'), (u'"Nintendo', u'O'), (u'Games"', u'O'), (u'department', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'product', u'O'), (u'developer.', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'continued', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'produce', u'O'), (u'popular', u'O'), (u'toys,', u'O'), (u'including', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Ultra', u'O'), (u'Machine,', u'O'), (u'Love', u'O'), (u'Tester', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'"Kousenjuu"', u'O'), (u'series', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'light', u'O'), (u'gun', u'O'), (u'games.', u'O'), (u'Despite', u'O'), (u'some', u'O'), (u'successful', u'O'), (u'products,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'struggled', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'meet', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'fast', u'O'), (u'development', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'manufacturing', u'O'), (u'turnaround', u'O'), (u'required', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'toy', u'O'), (u'market,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'fell', u'O'), (u'behind', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'well-established', u'O'), (u'companies', u'O'), (u'such', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'Bandai', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Tomy.', u'O')][(u'In', u'O'), (u'1973,', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'focus', u'O'), (u'shifted', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'family', u'O'), (u'entertainment', u'O'), (u'venues', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Laser', u'O'), (u'Clay', u'O'), (u'Shooting', u'O'), (u'System,', u'O'), (u'using', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'same', u'O'), (u'light', u'O'), (u'gun', u'O'), (u'technology', u'O'), (u'used', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u"Nintendo's", u'O'), (u'"Kousenjuu"', u'O'), (u'series', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'toys,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'set', u'O'), (u'up', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'abandoned', u'O'), (u'bowling', u'O'), (u'alleys.', u'O'), (u'Following', u'O'), (u'some', u'O'), (u'success,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'developed', u'O'), (u'several', u'O'), (u'more', u'O'), (u'light', u'O'), (u'gun', u'O'), (u'machines', u'O'), (u'(such', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'light', u'O'), (u'gun', u'O'), (u'shooter', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'"Wild', u'O'), (u'Gunman")', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'emerging', u'O'), (u'arcade', u'O'), (u'scene.', u'O'), (u'While', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Laser', u'O'), (u'Clay', u'O'), (u'Shooting', u'O'), (u'System', u'O'), (u'ranges', u'O'), (u'had', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'be', u'O'), (u'shut', u'O'), (u'down', u'O'), (u'following', u'O'), (u'excessive', u'O'), (u'costs,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'had', u'O'), (u'found', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'new', u'O'), (u'market.', u'O')][(u"Nintendo's", u'O'), (u'first', u'O'), (u'venture', u'O'), (u'into', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'gaming', u'O'), (u'industry', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'securing', u'O'), (u'rights', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'distribute', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Magnavox', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Odyssey', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Japan', u'LOCATION'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'1974.', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'began', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'produce', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'own', u'O'), (u'hardware', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'1977,', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Color', u'O'), (u'TV-Game', u'O'), (u'home', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'consoles.', u'O'), (u'Four', u'O'), (u'versions', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'these', u'O'), (u'consoles', u'O'), (u'were', u'O'), (u'produced,', u'O'), (u'each', u'O'), (u'including', u'O'), (u'variations', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'single', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'(for', u'O'), (u'example,', u'O'), (u'Color', u'O'), (u'TV', u'O'), (u'Game', u'O'), (u'6', u'O'), (u'featured', u'O'), (u'six', u'O'), (u'versions', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'"Light', u'O'), (u'Tennis").', u'O')][(u'A', u'O'), (u'student', u'O'), (u'product', u'O'), (u'developer', u'O'), (u'named', u'O'), (u'Shigeru', u'PERSON'), (u'Miyamoto', u'PERSON'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'hired', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'this', u'O'), (u'time.', u'O'), (u'He', u'O'), (u'worked', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Yokoi,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'one', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'his', u'O'), (u'first', u'O'), (u'tasks', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'design', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'casing', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'several', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Color', u'O'), (u'TV-Game', u'O'), (u'consoles.', u'O'), (u'Miyamoto', u'PERSON'), (u'went', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'create,', u'O'), (u'direct', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'produce', u'O'), (u'some', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u"Nintendo's", u'O'), (u'most', u'O'), (u'famous', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'become', u'O'), (u'one', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'most', u'O'), (u'recognizable', u'O'), (u'figures', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'industry.', u'O')][(u'In', u'O'), (u'1975,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'moved', u'O'), (u'into', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'arcade', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'industry', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'"EVR', u'O'), (u'Race",', u'O'), (u'designed', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'their', u'O'), (u'first', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'designer,', u'O'), (u'Genyo', u'O'), (u'Takeda,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'several', u'O'), (u'more', u'O'), (u'titles', u'O'), (u'followed.', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'had', u'O'), (u'some', u'O'), (u'small', u'O'), (u'success', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'this', u'O'), (u'venture,', u'O'), (u'but', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'release', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'"Donkey', u'O'), (u'Kong"', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'1981,', u'O'), (u'designed', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'Miyamoto,', u'O'), (u'changed', u'O'), (u"Nintendo's", u'O'), (u'fortunes', u'O'), (u'dramatically.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'success', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'many', u'O'), (u'licensing', u'O'), (u'opportunities', u'O'), (u'(such', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'ports', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Atari', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'2600,', u'O'), (u'Intellivision', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'ColecoVision)', u'O'), (u'gave', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'huge', u'O'), (u'boost', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'profit', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'addition,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'also', u'O'), (u'introduced', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'early', u'O'), (u'iteration', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Mario,', u'O'), (u'then', u'O'), (u'known', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Japan', u'LOCATION'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'Jumpman,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'eventual', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'mascot.', u'O')][(u'In', u'O'), (u'1979,', u'O'), (u'Gunpei', u'PERSON'), (u'Yokoi', u'PERSON'), (u'conceived', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'idea', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'handheld', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'game,', u'O'), (u'while', u'O'), (u'observing', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'fellow', u'O'), (u'bullet', u'O'), (u'train', u'O'), (u'commuter', u'O'), (u'who', u'O'), (u'passed', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'time', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'interacting', u'O'), (u'idly', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'portable', u'O'), (u'LCD', u'O'), (u'calculator,', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'gave', u'O'), (u'birth', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'"Game', u'O'), (u'&', u'O'), (u'Watch".', u'O'), (u'In', u'O'), (u'1980,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'launched', u'O'), (u'"Game', u'O'), (u'&', u'O'), (u'Watch"—a', u'O'), (u'handheld', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'series', u'O'), (u'developed', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'Yokoi.', u'O'), (u'These', u'O'), (u'systems', u'O'), (u'do', u'O'), (u'not', u'O'), (u'contain', u'O'), (u'interchangeable', u'O'), (u'cartridges', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'thus', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'hardware', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'tied', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'game.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'first', u'O'), (u'Game', u'O'), (u'&', u'O'), (u'Watch', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'released,', u'O'), (u'titled', u'O'), (u'"Ball",', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'distributed', u'O'), (u'worldwide.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'modern', u'O'), (u'"cross"', u'O'), (u'D-pad', u'O'), (u'design', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'developed', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'1982,', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'Yokoi', u'PERSON'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'"Donkey', u'O'), (u'Kong"', u'O'), (u'version.', u'O'), (u'Proven', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'be', u'O'), (u'popular,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'design', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'patented', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'Nintendo.', u'O'), (u'It', u'O'), (u'later', u'O'), (u'earned', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Technology', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'&', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Engineering', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Emmy', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Award.', u'ORGANIZATION')][(u'In', u'O'), (u'1983,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'launched', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Family', u'O'), (u'Computer', u'O'), (u'(colloquialized', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'"Famicom")', u'O'), (u'home', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Japan,', u'O'), (u'alongside', u'O'), (u'ports', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'most', u'O'), (u'popular', u'O'), (u'arcade', u'O'), (u'titles.', u'O'), (u'In', u'O'), (u'1985,', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'cosmetically', u'O'), (u'reworked', u'O'), (u'version', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'system', u'O'), (u'known', u'O'), (u'outside', u'O'), (u'Japan', u'LOCATION'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Entertainment', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'System', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'or', u'O'), (u'NES,', u'O'), (u'launched', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'North', u'LOCATION'), (u'America.', u'LOCATION'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'practice', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'bundling', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'system', u'O'), (u'along', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'select', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'helped', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'make', u'O'), (u'"Super', u'O'), (u'Mario', u'PERSON'), (u'Bros."', u'PERSON'), (u'one', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'best-selling', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'history.', u'O')][(u'In', u'O'), (u'1988,', u'O'), (u'Gunpei', u'PERSON'), (u'Yokoi', u'PERSON'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'his', u'O'), (u'team', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'R&D1', u'O'), (u'conceived', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'new', u'O'), (u'Game', u'O'), (u'Boy', u'O'), (u'handheld', u'O'), (u'system,', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'purpose', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'merging', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'two', u'O'), (u'very', u'O'), (u'successful', u'O'), (u'ideas', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Game', u'O'), (u'&', u'O'), (u"Watch's", u'O'), (u'portability', u'O'), (u'along', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u"NES's", u'O'), (u'cartridge', u'O'), (u'interchangeability.', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Game', u'O'), (u'Boy', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Japan', u'LOCATION'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'21', u'O'), (u'April', u'O'), (u'1989,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'North', u'LOCATION'), (u'America', u'LOCATION'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'31', u'O'), (u'July', u'O'), (u'1989.', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'of', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'America', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'president', u'O'), (u'Minoru', u'PERSON'), (u'Arakawa', u'PERSON'), (u'managed', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'deal', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'bundle', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'popular', u'O'), (u'third', u'O'), (u'party', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'"Tetris"', u'O'), (u'along', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Game', u'O'), (u'Boy,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'pair', u'O'), (u'launched', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'instant', u'O'), (u'success.', u'O')][(u'In', u'O'), (u'1989,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'announced', u'O'), (u'plans', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'release', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'successor', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Famicom,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Super', u'O'), (u'Famicom.', u'O'), (u'Based', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'16-bit', u'O'), (u'processor,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'boasted', u'O'), (u'significantly', u'O'), (u'superior', u'O'), (u'hardware', u'O'), (u'specifications', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'graphics,', u'O'), (u'sound,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'speed', u'O'), (u'over', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'original', u'O'), (u'8-bit', u'O'), (u'Famicom.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'system', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'also', u'O'), (u'said', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'have', u'O'), (u'backwards', u'O'), (u'compatibility', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'Famicom', u'O'), (u'games,', u'O'), (u'though', u'O'), (u'this', u'O'), (u'feature', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'ultimately', u'O'), (u'cut', u'O'), (u'upon', u'O'), (u'release.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'Super', u'O'), (u'Famicom', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'finally', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'relatively', u'O'), (u'late', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'market', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Japan', u'LOCATION'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'21', u'O'), (u'November', u'O'), (u'1990,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Super', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Entertainment', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'System', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'(officially', u'O'), (u'abbreviated', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Super', u'O'), (u'NES', u'O'), (u'or', u'O'), (u'SNES', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'commonly', u'O'), (u'shortened', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Super', u'O'), (u'Nintendo)', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'North', u'LOCATION'), (u'America', u'LOCATION'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'23', u'O'), (u'August', u'O'), (u'1991', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Europe', u'LOCATION'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'1992.', u'O'), (u'Its', u'O'), (u'main', u'O'), (u'rival', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'16-bit', u'O'), (u'Mega', u'O'), (u'Drive,', u'O'), (u'known', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'North', u'LOCATION'), (u'America', u'LOCATION'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'Genesis,', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'had', u'O'), (u'been', u'O'), (u'advertised', u'O'), (u'aggressively', u'O'), (u'against', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'nascent', u'O'), (u'8-bit', u'O'), (u'NES.', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'war', u'O'), (u'between', u'O'), (u'Sega', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'ensued', u'O'), (u'during', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'early', u'O'), (u'1990s.', u'O'), (u'From', u'O'), (u'1990', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'1992,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'opened', u'O'), (u'"World', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Nintendo"', u'O'), (u'shops', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'United', u'LOCATION'), (u'States', u'LOCATION'), (u'where', u'O'), (u'consumers', u'O'), (u'could', u'O'), (u'test', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'buy', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'products.', u'O')][(u'In', u'O'), (u'August', u'O'), (u'1993,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'announced', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u"SNES's", u'O'), (u'successor,', u'O'), (u'code-named', u'O'), (u'"Project', u'O'), (u'Reality".', u'O'), (u'Featuring', u'O'), (u'64-bit', u'O'), (u'graphics,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'new', u'O'), (u'system', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'developed', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'joint', u'O'), (u'venture', u'O'), (u'between', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'North-American-based', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'technology', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'Silicon', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Graphics.', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'system', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'announced', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'be', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'end', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'1995,', u'O'), (u'but', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'subsequently', u'O'), (u'delayed.', u'O'), (u'Meanwhile,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'continued', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Entertainment', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'System', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'family', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'release', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'NES-101,', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'smaller', u'O'), (u'redesign', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'original', u'O'), (u'NES.', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'also', u'O'), (u'announced', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'CD', u'O'), (u'drive', u'O'), (u'peripheral', u'O'), (u'called', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Super', u'O'), (u'NES', u'O'), (u'CD-ROM', u'O'), (u'Adapter,', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'co-developed', u'O'), (u'first', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'Sony', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'name', u'O'), (u'"Play', u'O'), (u'Station"', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'then', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'Philips.', u'O'), (u'Bearing', u'O'), (u'prototypes', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'joint', u'O'), (u'announcements', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Consumer', u'O'), (u'Electronics', u'O'), (u'Show,', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'track', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'1994', u'O'), (u'release,', u'O'), (u'but', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'controversially', u'O'), (u'cancelled.', u'O')][(u'During', u'O'), (u'1995,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'announced', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'had', u'O'), (u'sold', u'O'), (u'one', u'O'), (u'billion', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'cartridges', u'O'), (u'worldwide,', u'O'), (u'ten', u'O'), (u'percent', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'those', u'O'), (u'being', u'O'), (u'from', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Mario', u'PERSON'), (u'franchise.', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'deemed', u'O'), (u'1994', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'"Year', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Cartridge".', u'O'), (u'To', u'O'), (u'further', u'O'), (u'their', u'O'), (u'support', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'cartridges,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'announced', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'Project', u'O'), (u'Reality,', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'had', u'O'), (u'now', u'O'), (u'been', u'O'), (u'renamed', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Ultra', u'O'), (u'64,', u'O'), (u'would', u'O'), (u'not', u'O'), (u'use', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'CD', u'O'), (u'format', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'expected,', u'O'), (u'but', u'O'), (u'would', u'O'), (u'rather', u'O'), (u'use', u'O'), (u'cartridges', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'primary', u'O'), (u'media', u'O'), (u'format.', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'IRD', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'general', u'O'), (u'manager', u'O'), (u'Genyo', u'PERSON'), (u'Takeda', u'PERSON'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'impressed', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'development', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u"Rare's", u'O'), (u'progress', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'real-time', u'O'), (u'3D', u'O'), (u'graphics', u'O'), (u'technology,', u'O'), (u'using', u'O'), (u'state', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'art', u'O'), (u'Silicon', u'O'), (u'Graphics', u'O'), (u'workstations.', u'O'), (u'As', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'result,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'bought', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'25%', u'O'), (u'stake', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'company,', u'O'), (u'eventually', u'O'), (u'expanding', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'49%,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'offered', u'O'), (u'their', u'O'), (u'catalogue', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'characters', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'create', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'CGI', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'around,', u'O'), (u'making', u'O'), (u'Rare', u'O'), (u"Nintendo's", u'O'), (u'first', u'O'), (u'western-based', u'O'), (u'second-party', u'O'), (u'developer.', u'O'), (u'Their', u'O'), (u'first', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'partners', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'"Donkey', u'O'), (u'Kong', u'O'), (u'Country".', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'critical', u'O'), (u'success', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'sold', u'O'), (u'over', u'O'), (u'eight', u'O'), (u'million', u'O'), (u'copies', u'O'), (u'worldwide,', u'O'), (u'making', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'second', u'O'), (u'best-selling', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'SNES', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'library.', u'O'), (u'In', u'O'), (u'September', u'O'), (u'1994,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo,', u'O'), (u'along', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'six', u'O'), (u'other', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'giants', u'O'), (u'including', u'O'), (u'Sega,', u'O'), (u'Electronic', u'O'), (u'Arts,', u'O'), (u'Atari,', u'O'), (u'Acclaim,', u'O'), (u'Philips,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'3DO', u'O'), (u'approached', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'United', u'LOCATION'), (u'States', u'LOCATION'), (u'Senate', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'demanded', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'ratings', u'O'), (u'system', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'be', u'O'), (u'enforced,', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'prompted', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'decision', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'create', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Entertainment', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Software', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Rating', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Board.', u'ORGANIZATION')][(u'Aiming', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'produce', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'affordable', u'O'), (u'virtual', u'O'), (u'reality', u'O'), (u'console,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Virtual', u'O'), (u'Boy', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'1995,', u'O'), (u'designed', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'Gunpei', u'PERSON'), (u'Yokoi.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'consists', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'head-mounted', u'O'), (u'semi-portable', u'O'), (u'system', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'one', u'O'), (u'red-colored', u'O'), (u'screen', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'each', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u"user's", u'O'), (u'eyes,', u'O'), (u'featuring', u'O'), (u'stereoscopic', u'O'), (u'graphics.', u'O'), (u'Games', u'O'), (u'are', u'O'), (u'viewed', u'O'), (u'through', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'binocular', u'O'), (u'eyepiece', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'controlled', u'O'), (u'using', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'affixed', u'O'), (u'gamepad.', u'O'), (u'Critics', u'O'), (u'were', u'O'), (u'generally', u'O'), (u'disappointed', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'quality', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'red-colored', u'O'), (u'graphics,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'complained', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'gameplay-induced', u'O'), (u'headaches.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'system', u'O'), (u'sold', u'O'), (u'poorly', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'quietly', u'O'), (u'discontinued.', u'O'), (u'Amid', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u"system's", u'O'), (u'failure,', u'O'), (u'Yokoi', u'PERSON'), (u'retired', u'O'), (u'from', u'O'), (u'Nintendo.', u'O'), (u'During', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'same', u'O'), (u'year,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'launched', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Satellaview', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Japan,', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'peripheral', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Super', u'O'), (u'Famicom.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'accessory', u'O'), (u'allowed', u'O'), (u'users', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'play', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'via', u'O'), (u'broadcast', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'set', u'O'), (u'period', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'time.', u'O'), (u'Various', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'were', u'O'), (u'made', u'O'), (u'exclusively', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'platform,', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'well', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'various', u'O'), (u'remakes.', u'O')][(u'In', u'O'), (u'1996,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Ultra', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'64', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'64', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Japan', u'LOCATION'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'North', u'LOCATION'), (u'America.', u'LOCATION'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'later', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Europe', u'LOCATION'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Australia', u'LOCATION'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'1997.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'64', u'O'), (u'continued', u'O'), (u'what', u'O'), (u'had', u'O'), (u'become', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'tradition', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'hardware', u'O'), (u'design', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'focused', u'O'), (u'less', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'high', u'O'), (u'performance', u'O'), (u'specifications', u'O'), (u'than', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'design', u'O'), (u'innovations', u'O'), (u'intended', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'inspire', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'development.', u'O'), (u'With', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'market', u'O'), (u'shares', u'O'), (u'slipping', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Sega', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Saturn', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'partner-turned-rival', u'O'), (u'Sony', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'PlayStation,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'revitalized', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'brand', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'launching', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'$185', u'O'), (u'million', u'O'), (u'marketing', u'O'), (u'campaign', u'O'), (u'centered', u'O'), (u'around', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'"Play', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'Loud"', u'O'), (u'slogan.', u'O'), (u'During', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'same', u'O'), (u'year,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'also', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Game', u'O'), (u'Boy', u'O'), (u'Pocket', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Japan,', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'smaller', u'O'), (u'version', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Game', u'O'), (u'Boy', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'generated', u'O'), (u'more', u'O'), (u'sales', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'platform.', u'O'), (u'On', u'O'), (u'4', u'O'), (u'October', u'O'), (u'1997,', u'O'), (u'famed', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'developer', u'O'), (u'Gunpei', u'PERSON'), (u'Yokoi', u'PERSON'), (u'died', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'car', u'O'), (u'crash.', u'O'), (u'In', u'O'), (u'1997,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'SNS-101', u'O'), (u'(called', u'O'), (u'Super', u'O'), (u'Famicom', u'O'), (u'Jr.', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Japan),', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'smaller', u'O'), (u'redesigned', u'O'), (u'version', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Super', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Entertainment', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'System.', u'ORGANIZATION')][(u'In', u'O'), (u'1998,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'successor', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Game', u'O'), (u'Boy,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Game', u'O'), (u'Boy', u'O'), (u'Color,', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'released.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'system', u'O'), (u'had', u'O'), (u'improved', u'O'), (u'technical', u'O'), (u'specifications', u'O'), (u'allowing', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'run', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'made', u'O'), (u'specifically', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'system', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'well', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Game', u'O'), (u'Boy,', u'O'), (u'albeit', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'added', u'O'), (u'color.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'Game', u'O'), (u'Boy', u'O'), (u'Camera', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Printer', u'O'), (u'were', u'O'), (u'also', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'accessories.', u'O'), (u'In', u'O'), (u'October', u'O'), (u'1998,', u'O'), (u'Retro', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Studios', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'founded', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'alliance', u'O'), (u'between', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'former', u'O'), (u'Iguana', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Entertainment', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'founder', u'O'), (u'Jeff', u'PERSON'), (u'Spangenberg.', u'PERSON'), (u'Nintendo', u'PERSON'), (u'saw', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'opportunity', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'new', u'O'), (u'studio', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'create', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'upcoming', u'O'), (u'GameCube', u'O'), (u'targeting', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'older', u'O'), (u'demographic,', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'same', u'O'), (u'vein', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'Iguana', u'O'), (u"Entertainment's", u'O'), (u'successful', u'O'), (u'""', u'O'), (u'series', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'64.', u'O')][(u'In', u'O'), (u'2001,', u'O'), (u'just', u'O'), (u'three', u'O'), (u'years', u'O'), (u'later,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'introduced', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'redesigned', u'O'), (u'Game', u'O'), (u'Boy', u'O'), (u'Advance.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'same', u'O'), (u'year,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'also', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'GameCube', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'lukewarm', u'O'), (u'sales,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'ultimately', u'O'), (u'failed', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'regain', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'market', u'O'), (u'share', u'O'), (u'lost', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'64.', u'O'), (u'When', u'O'), (u'Yamauchi,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u"company's", u'O'), (u'president', u'O'), (u'since', u'O'), (u'1949,', u'O'), (u'retired', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'24', u'O'), (u'May', u'O'), (u'2002,', u'O'), (u'Satoru', u'PERSON'), (u'Iwata', u'PERSON'), (u'succeeded', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u"Nintendo's", u'O'), (u'fourth', u'O'), (u'president,', u'O'), (u'becoming', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'first', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'president', u'O'), (u'who', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'unrelated', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Yamauchi', u'PERSON'), (u'family', u'O'), (u'through', u'O'), (u'blood', u'O'), (u'or', u'O'), (u'marriage', u'O'), (u'since', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'founding', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'1889.', u'O')][(u'In', u'O'), (u'2003,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Game', u'O'), (u'Boy', u'O'), (u'Advance', u'O'), (u'SP,', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'fourth', u'O'), (u'handheld', u'O'), (u'system.', u'O')][(u'In', u'O'), (u'2004,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'DS,', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'fourth', u'O'), (u'major', u'O'), (u'handheld', u'O'), (u'system.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'DS', u'O'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'dual', u'O'), (u'screened', u'O'), (u'handheld', u'O'), (u'featuring', u'O'), (u'touch', u'O'), (u'screen', u'O'), (u'capabilities,', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'respond', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'either', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'stylus', u'O'), (u'or', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'touch', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'finger.', u'O'), (u'Former', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'president', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'now', u'O'), (u'chairman', u'O'), (u'Hiroshi', u'PERSON'), (u'Yamauchi', u'PERSON'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'translated', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'GameScience', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'explaining,', u'O'), (u'"If', u'O'), (u'we', u'O'), (u'can', u'O'), (u'increase', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'scope', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'industry,', u'O'), (u'we', u'O'), (u'can', u'O'), (u're-energise', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'global', u'O'), (u'market', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'lift', u'O'), (u'Japan', u'LOCATION'), (u'out', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'depression', u'O'), (u'–', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'is', u'O'), (u"Nintendo's", u'O'), (u'mission."', u'O'), (u'Regarding', u'O'), (u'lukewarm', u'O'), (u'GameCube', u'O'), (u'sales', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'had', u'O'), (u'yielded', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u"company's", u'O'), (u'first', u'O'), (u'reported', u'O'), (u'operating', u'O'), (u'loss', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'over', u'O'), (u'100', u'O'), (u'years,', u'O'), (u'Yamauchi', u'PERSON'), (u'continued:', u'O'), (u'"The', u'O'), (u'DS', u'O'), (u'represents', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'critical', u'O'), (u'moment', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u"Nintendo's", u'O'), (u'success', u'O'), (u'over', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'next', u'O'), (u'two', u'O'), (u'years.', u'O'), (u'If', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'succeeds,', u'O'), (u'we', u'O'), (u'rise', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'heavens,', u'O'), (u'if', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'fails,', u'O'), (u'we', u'O'), (u'sink', u'O'), (u'into', u'O'), (u'hell."', u'O'), (u'Thanks', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'titles', u'O'), (u'such', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'Nintendogs', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Mario', u'PERSON'), (u'Kart', u'PERSON'), (u'DS,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'DS', u'O'), (u'became', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'success.', u'O'), (u'In', u'O'), (u'2005,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Game', u'O'), (u'Boy', u'O'), (u'Micro', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'North', u'LOCATION'), (u'America,', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'redesign', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Game', u'O'), (u'Boy', u'O'), (u'Advance.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'last', u'O'), (u'system', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Game', u'O'), (u'Boy', u'O'), (u'line,', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'also', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'smallest', u'O'), (u'Game', u'O'), (u'Boy,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'least', u'O'), (u'successful.', u'O'), (u'In', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'middle', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'2005,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'opened', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'World', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Store', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'New', u'LOCATION'), (u'York', u'LOCATION'), (u'City,', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'would', u'O'), (u'sell', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'games,', u'O'), (u'present', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'museum', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'history,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'host', u'O'), (u'public', u'O'), (u'parties', u'O'), (u'such', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'product', u'O'), (u'launches.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'store', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'renovated', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'renamed', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'New', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'York', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'2016.', u'O')][(u'In', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'first', u'O'), (u'half', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'2006,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'DS', u'O'), (u'Lite,', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'version', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'original', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'DS', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'lighter', u'O'), (u'weight,', u'O'), (u'brighter', u'O'), (u'screen,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'better', u'O'), (u'battery', u'O'), (u'life.', u'O'), (u'In', u'O'), (u'addition', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'this', u'O'), (u'streamlined', u'O'), (u'design,', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'prolific', u'O'), (u'subset', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'casual', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'appealed', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'masses,', u'O'), (u'such', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'"Brain', u'O'), (u'Age"', u'O'), (u'series.', u'O'), (u'Meanwhile,', u'O'), (u'"New', u'O'), (u'Super', u'O'), (u'Mario', u'PERSON'), (u'Bros."', u'PERSON'), (u'provided', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'substantial', u'O'), (u'addition', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'"Mario"', u'O'), (u'series', u'O'), (u'when', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'launched', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'top', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'sales', u'O'), (u'charts.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'successful', u'O'), (u'direction', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'DS', u'O'), (u'had', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'big', u'O'), (u'influence', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u"Nintendo's", u'O'), (u'next', u'O'), (u'home', u'O'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'(including', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'common', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Wi-Fi', u'O'), (u'Connection),', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'had', u'O'), (u'been', u'O'), (u'codenamed', u'O'), (u'"Revolution"', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'now', u'O'), (u'renamed', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'"Wii".', u'O'), (u'In', u'O'), (u'August', u'O'), (u'2006,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'published', u'O'), (u'ES,', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'now-dormant,', u'O'), (u'open', u'O'), (u'source', u'O'), (u'research', u'O'), (u'operating', u'O'), (u'system', u'O'), (u'project', u'O'), (u'designed', u'O'), (u'around', u'O'), (u'web', u'O'), (u'application', u'O'), (u'integration', u'O'), (u'but', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'no', u'O'), (u'specific', u'O'), (u'purpose.', u'O')][(u'In', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'latter', u'O'), (u'half', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'2006,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'backward-compatible', u'O'), (u'successor', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'GameCube.', u'O'), (u'Based', u'O'), (u'upon', u'O'), (u'intricate', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'Remote', u'O'), (u'motion', u'O'), (u'controls', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'balance', u'O'), (u'board,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'inspired', u'O'), (u'several', u'O'), (u'new', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'franchises,', u'O'), (u'some', u'O'), (u'targeted', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'entirely', u'O'), (u'new', u'O'), (u'market', u'O'), (u'segments', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'casual', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'fitness', u'O'), (u'gaming.', u'O'), (u'At', u'O'), (u'more', u'O'), (u'than', u'O'), (u'100', u'O'), (u'million', u'O'), (u'units,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'best', u'O'), (u'selling', u'O'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'seventh', u'O'), (u'generation,', u'O'), (u'regaining', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'market', u'O'), (u'share', u'O'), (u'lost', u'O'), (u'during', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'tenures', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'64', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'GameCube.', u'O')][(u'On', u'O'), (u'1', u'O'), (u'May', u'O'), (u'2007,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'acquired', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'80%', u'O'), (u'stake', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'development', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'Monolith', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Soft,', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'previously', u'O'), (u'owned', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'Bandai', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Namco.', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Monolith', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Soft', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'best', u'O'), (u'known', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'developing', u'O'), (u'role-playing', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'such', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Xenosaga', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Baten', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Kaitos', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'series.', u'O')][(u'During', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'holiday', u'O'), (u'season', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'2008,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'followed', u'O'), (u'up', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'success', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'DS', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'release', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'DSi', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Japan.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'system', u'O'), (u'features', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'more', u'O'), (u'powerful', u'O'), (u'CPU', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'more', u'O'), (u'RAM,', u'O'), (u'two', u'O'), (u'cameras,', u'O'), (u'one', u'O'), (u'facing', u'O'), (u'towards', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'player', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'one', u'O'), (u'facing', u'O'), (u'outwards,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'had', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'online', u'O'), (u'distribution', u'O'), (u'store', u'O'), (u'called', u'O'), (u'DSiWare.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'DSi', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'later', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'worldwide', u'O'), (u'during', u'O'), (u'2009.', u'O'), (u'In', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'latter', u'O'), (u'half', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'2009,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'DSi', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'XL', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Japan,', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'larger', u'O'), (u'version', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'DSi.', u'O'), (u'This', u'O'), (u'updated', u'O'), (u'system', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'later', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'worldwide', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'2010.', u'O')][(u'In', u'O'), (u'2011,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'3DS,', u'O'), (u'based', u'O'), (u'upon', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'glasses-free', u'O'), (u'3D', u'O'), (u'display.', u'O'), (u'In', u'O'), (u'February', u'O'), (u'2012,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'acquired', u'O'), (u'Mobiclip,', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'France-based', u'O'), (u'research', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'development', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'specialized', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'highly', u'O'), (u'optimized', u'O'), (u'software', u'O'), (u'technologies', u'O'), (u'such', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'compression.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u"company's", u'O'), (u'name', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'later', u'O'), (u'changed', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'European', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Research', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'&', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Development.', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'During', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'fourth', u'O'), (u'quarter', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'2012,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'U.', u'O'), (u'It', u'O'), (u'sold', u'O'), (u'slower', u'O'), (u'than', u'O'), (u'expected,', u'O'), (u'despite', u'O'), (u'being', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'first', u'O'), (u'eighth', u'O'), (u'generation', u'O'), (u'console.', u'O'), (u'By', u'O'), (u'September', u'O'), (u'2013,', u'O'), (u'however,', u'O'), (u'sales', u'O'), (u'had', u'O'), (u'rebounded.', u'O'), (u'Intending', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'broaden', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'3DS', u'O'), (u'market,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'released', u'O'), (u"2013's", u'O'), (u'cost-reduced', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'2DS.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'2DS', u'O'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'compatible', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'but', u'O'), (u'lacks', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u"3DS's", u'O'), (u'more', u'O'), (u'expensive', u'O'), (u'but', u'O'), (u'cosmetic', u'O'), (u'autostereoscopic', u'O'), (u'3D', u'O'), (u'feature.', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'also', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'Mini,', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'cheaper', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'non-networked', u'O'), (u'redesign', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Wii.', u'O')][(u'On', u'O'), (u'25', u'O'), (u'September', u'O'), (u'2013,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'announced', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'had', u'O'), (u'purchased', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'28%', u'O'), (u'stake', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Panasonic', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'spin-off', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'called', u'O'), (u'PUX', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Corporation.', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'specializes', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'face', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'voice', u'O'), (u'recognition', u'O'), (u'technology,', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'intends', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'improve', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'usability', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'future', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'systems.', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'has', u'O'), (u'also', u'O'), (u'worked', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'this', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'past', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'create', u'O'), (u'character', u'O'), (u'recognition', u'O'), (u'software', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'DS', u'O'), (u'touchscreen.', u'O'), (u'After', u'O'), (u'announcing', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'30%', u'O'), (u'dive', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'profits', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'April', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'December', u'O'), (u'2013', u'O'), (u'period,', u'O'), (u'president', u'O'), (u'Satoru', u'PERSON'), (u'Iwata', u'PERSON'), (u'announced', u'O'), (u'he', u'O'), (u'would', u'O'), (u'take', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'50%', u'O'), (u'pay-cut,', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'other', u'O'), (u'executives', u'O'), (u'seeing', u'O'), (u'reductions', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'20%–30%.', u'O')][(u'In', u'O'), (u'January', u'O'), (u'2015,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'announced', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'exit', u'O'), (u'from', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Brazilian', u'O'), (u'market', u'O'), (u'after', u'O'), (u'four', u'O'), (u'years', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'distributing', u'O'), (u'products', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'country.', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'cited', u'O'), (u'high', u'O'), (u'import', u'O'), (u'duties', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'lack', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'local', u'O'), (u'manufacturing', u'O'), (u'operation', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'reasons', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'leaving.', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'continues', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'partnership', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'Juegos', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'de', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Video', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Latinoam\xe9rica', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'distribute', u'O'), (u'products', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'rest', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Latin', u'LOCATION'), (u'America.', u'LOCATION')][(u'On', u'O'), (u'11', u'O'), (u'July', u'O'), (u'2015,', u'O'), (u'Iwata', u'PERSON'), (u'died', u'O'), (u'from', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'bile', u'O'), (u'duct', u'O'), (u'tumor', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'age', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'55.', u'O'), (u'Following', u'O'), (u'his', u'O'), (u'death,', u'O'), (u'representative', u'O'), (u'directors', u'O'), (u'Genyo', u'PERSON'), (u'Takeda', u'PERSON'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Shigeru', u'PERSON'), (u'Miyamoto', u'PERSON'), (u'jointly', u'O'), (u'led', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'interim', u'O'), (u'basis', u'O'), (u'until', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'appointment', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Tatsumi', u'PERSON'), (u'Kimishima', u'PERSON'), (u'as', u'O'), (u"Iwata's", u'O'), (u'successor', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'16', u'O'), (u'September', u'O'), (u'2015.', u'O'), (u'In', u'O'), (u'addition', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u"Kimishima's", u'O'), (u'appointment,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u"company's", u'O'), (u'management', u'O'), (u'organization', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'also', u'O'), (u'restructured—Miyamoto', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'named', u'O'), (u'"Creative', u'O'), (u'Fellow"', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Takeda', u'PERSON'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'named', u'O'), (u'"Technology', u'O'), (u'Fellow".', u'O')][(u'On', u'O'), (u'17', u'O'), (u'March', u'O'), (u'2015,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'announced', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'partnership', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'Japanese', u'O'), (u'mobile', u'O'), (u'developer', u'O'), (u'DeNA', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'produce', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'smart', u'O'), (u'devices.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'first', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'these,', u'O'), (u'"Miitomo",', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'March', u'O'), (u'2016.', u'O')][(u'On', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'same', u'O'), (u'day,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'announced', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'new', u'O'), (u'"dedicated', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'platform', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'brand', u'O'), (u'new', u'O'), (u'concept"', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'codename', u'O'), (u'"NX"', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'would', u'O'), (u'be', u'O'), (u'further', u'O'), (u'revealed', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'2016.', u'O'), (u'Reggie', u'PERSON'), (u'Fils-Aim\xe9,', u'O'), (u'president', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'America,', u'O'), (u'referred', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'NX', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'"our', u'O'), (u'next', u'O'), (u'home', u'O'), (u'console"', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'June', u'O'), (u'2015', u'O'), (u'interview', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'"The', u'O'), (u'Wall', u'O'), (u'Street', u'O'), (u'Journal".', u'O'), (u'In', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'later', u'O'), (u'16', u'O'), (u'October', u'O'), (u'2015', u'O'), (u'article,', u'O'), (u'"The', u'O'), (u'Wall', u'O'), (u'Street', u'O'), (u'Journal"', u'O'), (u'relayed', u'O'), (u'speculation', u'O'), (u'from', u'O'), (u'unnamed', u'O'), (u'inside', u'O'), (u'sources', u'O'), (u'that,', u'O'), (u'although', u'O'), (u'unknown,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'NX', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'intended', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'feature', u'O'), (u'"industry', u'O'), (u'leading"', u'O'), (u'hardware', u'O'), (u'specifications', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'be', u'O'), (u'usable', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'both', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'home', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'portable', u'O'), (u'console.', u'O'), (u'It', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'also', u'O'), (u'reported', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'had', u'O'), (u'begun', u'O'), (u'distributing', u'O'), (u'software', u'O'), (u'development', u'O'), (u'kits', u'O'), (u'(SDKs)', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'NX', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'third-party', u'O'), (u'developers,', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'unnamed', u'O'), (u'source', u'O'), (u'further', u'O'), (u'speculating', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'these', u'O'), (u'moves', u'O'), (u'"[suggest', u'O'), (u'that]', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'track', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'introduce', u'O'), (u'[NX]', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'early', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'[2016]."', u'O'), (u'At', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u"investor's", u'O'), (u'meeting', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'27', u'O'), (u'April', u'O'), (u'2016,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'announced', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'NX', u'O'), (u'would', u'O'), (u'be', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'worldwide', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'March', u'O'), (u'2017.', u'O'), (u'In', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'interview', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'Asahi', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Shimbun', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'May', u'O'), (u'2016,', u'O'), (u'Kimishima', u'O'), (u'stated', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'NX', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'new', u'O'), (u'concept', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'would', u'O'), (u'not', u'O'), (u'succeed', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'3DS', u'O'), (u'or', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'U', u'O'), (u'product', u'O'), (u'lines.', u'O'), (u'At', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u"shareholders'", u'O'), (u'meeting', u'O'), (u'following', u'O'), (u'E3', u'O'), (u'2016,', u'O'), (u'Shigeru', u'PERSON'), (u'Miyamoto', u'PERSON'), (u'stated', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'chose', u'O'), (u'not', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'present', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'NX', u'O'), (u'during', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'conference', u'O'), (u'due', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'concerns', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'competitors', u'O'), (u'could', u'O'), (u'copy', u'O'), (u'from', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'if', u'O'), (u'they', u'O'), (u'revealed', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'too', u'O'), (u'soon.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'same', u'O'), (u'day,', u'O'), (u'Kimishima', u'PERSON'), (u'also', u'O'), (u'revealed', u'O'), (u'during', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Q&A', u'O'), (u'session', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'investors', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'they', u'O'), (u'were', u'O'), (u'also', u'O'), (u'researching', u'O'), (u'virtual', u'O'), (u'reality.', u'O')][(u'In', u'O'), (u'May', u'O'), (u'2015,', u'O'), (u'Universal', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Parks', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'&', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Resorts', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'announced', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'partnering', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'create', u'O'), (u'attractions', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'Universal', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Parks', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'based', u'O'), (u'upon', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'properties.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'following', u'O'), (u'year', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'also', u'O'), (u'expressed', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'desire', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'enter', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'animated', u'O'), (u'film', u'O'), (u'market.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'first', u'O'), (u'attraction', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'be', u'O'), (u'created', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'Universal', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Parks', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'known', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'Super', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'World,', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'will', u'O'), (u'be', u'O'), (u'completed', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'2020.', u'O')][(u'In', u'O'), (u'July', u'O'), (u'2016,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'announced', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'bringing', u'O'), (u'back', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'NES', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'form', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'NES', u'O'), (u'Classic', u'O'), (u'Edition', u'O'), (u'(called', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'O'), (u'Classic', u'O'), (u'Mini', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Europe).', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'plug-and-play', u'O'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'will', u'O'), (u'support', u'O'), (u'HDMI,', u'O'), (u'two-player', u'O'), (u'modes,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'have', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'controller', u'O'), (u'similar', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'original', u'O'), (u'NES', u'O'), (u'controller.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'controller', u'O'), (u'would', u'O'), (u'be', u'O'), (u'able', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'connect', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'Remote', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'use', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'U', u'O'), (u'Virtual', u'O'), (u'Console', u'O'), (u'titles.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'NES', u'O'), (u'Classic', u'O'), (u'Edition', u'O'), (u'came', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'30', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'pre-installed,', u'O'), (u'including', u'O'), (u'"Final', u'O'), (u'Fantasy",', u'O'), (u'"Kid', u'O'), (u'Icarus",', u'O'), (u'"The', u'O'), (u'Legend', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Zelda",', u'O'), (u'"",', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'"Dr.', u'O'), (u'Mario",', u'O'), (u'among', u'O'), (u'others.', u'O'), (u'It', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'November', u'O'), (u'2016.', u'O'), (u'Additional', u'O'), (u'controllers', u'O'), (u'were', u'O'), (u'also', u'O'), (u'available.', u'O')][(u'The', u'O'), (u'July', u'O'), (u'2016', u'O'), (u'release', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'"Pok\xe9mon', u'O'), (u'Go"', u'O'), (u'mobile', u'O'), (u'app', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'Niantic', u'LOCATION'), (u'caused', u'O'), (u'shares', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'double,', u'O'), (u'due', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'investor', u'O'), (u'misunderstanding', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'software', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'property', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Nintendo.', u'O'), (u'Later', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'month,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'statement', u'O'), (u'clarifying', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'relation', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'Niantic,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'stated', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'owned', u'O'), (u'32%', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Pok\xe9mon', u'O'), (u'intellectual', u'O'), (u'property', u'O'), (u'owner', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'Pok\xe9mon', u'O'), (u'Company,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'though', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'would', u'O'), (u'receive', u'O'), (u'some', u'O'), (u'licensing', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'other', u'O'), (u'revenues', u'O'), (u'from', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'expected', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'impact', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u"Nintendo's", u'O'), (u'total', u'O'), (u'income', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'be', u'O'), (u'limited.', u'O'), (u'As', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'result', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'statement', u'O'), (u"Nintendo's", u'O'), (u'share', u'O'), (u'price', u'O'), (u'fell', u'O'), (u'substantially,', u'O'), (u'losing', u'O'), (u'17%', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'one', u'O'), (u'day', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'trading.', u'O'), (u'After', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'reduction', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'shareprice', u'O'), (u'from', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'"Pok\xe9mon', u'O'), (u'Go"', u'O'), (u'peak,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'still', u'O'), (u'valued', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'over', u'O'), (u'100', u'O'), (u'times', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'net', u'O'), (u'income,', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'price–earnings', u'O'), (u'ratio', u'O'), (u'greatly', u'O'), (u'exceeding', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'average', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Nikkei', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'225.', u'O'), (u'Analysts', u'O'), (u'speaking', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Bloomberg', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'L.P.', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'"Financial', u'O'), (u'Times"', u'O'), (u'both', u'O'), (u'commented', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'potential', u'O'), (u'future', u'O'), (u'value', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u"Nintendo's", u'O'), (u'IP', u'O'), (u'if', u'O'), (u'transferred', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'mobile', u'O'), (u'phone', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'business.', u'O')][(u'In', u'O'), (u'August', u'O'), (u'2016,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'of', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'America', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'sold', u'O'), (u'90%', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'controlling', u'O'), (u'stake', u'O'), (u'(55%)', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Seattle', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Mariners', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'group', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'investors', u'O'), (u'led', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'mobile', u'O'), (u'phone', u'O'), (u'businessman', u'O'), (u'John', u'PERSON'), (u'Stanton', u'PERSON'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'$640', u'O'), (u'million.', u'O')][(u'After', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'announcement', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'mobile', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'"Super', u'O'), (u'Mario', u'PERSON'), (u'Run"', u'PERSON'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'September', u'O'), (u'2016,', u'O'), (u"Nintendo's", u'O'), (u'stock', u'O'), (u'soared', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'just', u'O'), (u'under', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'recent', u'O'), (u'high', u'O'), (u'point', u'O'), (u'after', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'release', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'success', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'"Pok\xe9mon', u'O'), (u'Go"', u'O'), (u'earlier', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'year,', u'O'), (u'something', u'O'), (u'noted', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'journalists', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'even', u'O'), (u'more', u'O'), (u'significant', u'O'), (u'than', u'O'), (u'"Pok\xe9mon', u'O'), (u'Go",', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'"Super', u'O'), (u'Mario', u'PERSON'), (u'Run"', u'PERSON'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'developed', u'O'), (u'in-house', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'Nintendo,', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'not', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'case', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'"Pok\xe9mon', u'O'), (u'Go".', u'O'), (u'In', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'December', u'O'), (u'2016', u'O'), (u'interview', u'O'), (u'prior', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'release', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'"Super', u'O'), (u'Mario', u'PERSON'), (u'Run",', u'PERSON'), (u'Miyamoto', u'PERSON'), (u'explained', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'believed', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'some', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'their', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'franchises,', u'O'), (u'"the', u'O'), (u'longer', u'O'), (u'you', u'O'), (u'continue', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'make', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'series,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'more', u'O'), (u'complex', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'gameplay', u'O'), (u'becomes,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'harder', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'becomes', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'new', u'O'), (u'players', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'be', u'O'), (u'able', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'get', u'O'), (u'into', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'series",', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'sees', u'O'), (u'mobile', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'simplified', u'O'), (u'controls,', u'O'), (u'such', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'"Super', u'O'), (u'Mario', u'PERSON'), (u'Run",', u'PERSON'), (u'not', u'O'), (u'only', u'O'), (u'allows', u'O'), (u'them', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'"make', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'broadest', u'O'), (u'audience', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'people', u'O'), (u'could', u'O'), (u'play",', u'O'), (u'but', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'also', u'O'), (u'reintroduce', u'O'), (u'these', u'O'), (u'properties', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'newer', u'O'), (u'audiences', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'draw', u'O'), (u'them', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'their', u'O'), (u'consoles.', u'O')][(u'On', u'O'), (u'20', u'O'), (u'October', u'O'), (u'2016,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'preview', u'O'), (u'trailer', u'O'), (u'about', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'NX,', u'O'), (u'revealing', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'official', u'O'), (u'name', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'be', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Switch.', u'O'), (u'According', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Fils-Aim\xe9,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'gave', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'developers', u'O'), (u'new', u'O'), (u'abilities', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'bring', u'O'), (u'their', u'O'), (u'creative', u'O'), (u'concepts', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'life', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'opening', u'O'), (u'up', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'concept', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'gaming', u'O'), (u'without', u'O'), (u'limits.', u'O'), (u'In', u'O'), (u'December', u'O'), (u'2016,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'"Super', u'O'), (u'Mario', u'PERSON'), (u'Run"', u'PERSON'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'iOS', u'O'), (u'devices,', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'surpassing', u'O'), (u'over', u'O'), (u'50', u'O'), (u'million', u'O'), (u'downloads', u'O'), (u'within', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'week', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'release.', u'O'), (u'Due', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'success', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'title,', u'O'), (u'Kimishima', u'PERSON'), (u'stated', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'would', u'O'), (u'begin', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'release', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'couple', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'mobile', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'each', u'O'), (u'year', u'O'), (u'from', u'O'), (u'then', u'O'), (u'on.', u'O')][(u'Released', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'1977,', u'O'), (u"Japan's", u'O'), (u'highest', u'O'), (u'selling', u'O'), (u'first', u'O'), (u'generation', u'O'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'is', u'O'), (u"Nintendo's", u'O'), (u'Color', u'O'), (u'TV', u'O'), (u'Game,', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'3', u'O'), (u'million', u'O'), (u'units', u'O'), (u'sold.', u'O')][(u'The', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Entertainment', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'System', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'(abbreviated', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'NES)', u'O'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'8-bit', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'console,', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'North', u'LOCATION'), (u'America', u'LOCATION'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'1985,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Europe', u'LOCATION'), (u'throughout', u'O'), (u'1986', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'1987.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'initially', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Japan', u'LOCATION'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Family', u'O'), (u'Computer', u'O'), (u'(abbreviated', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'Famicom)', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'1983.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'best-selling', u'O'), (u'gaming', u'O'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'time,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'NES', u'O'), (u'helped', u'O'), (u'revitalize', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'US', u'LOCATION'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'industry', u'O'), (u'following', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'crash', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'1983.', u'O'), (u'With', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'NES,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'introduced', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'now-standard', u'O'), (u'business', u'O'), (u'model', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'licensing', u'O'), (u'third-party', u'O'), (u'developers,', u'O'), (u'authorizing', u'O'), (u'them', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'produce', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'distribute', u'O'), (u'titles', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u"Nintendo's", u'O'), (u'platform.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'NES', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'bundled', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'"Super', u'O'), (u'Mario', u'PERSON'), (u'Bros.",', u'PERSON'), (u'one', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'best-selling', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'all', u'O'), (u'time,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'received', u'O'), (u'ports', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u"Nintendo's", u'O'), (u'most', u'O'), (u'popular', u'O'), (u'arcade', u'O'), (u'titles.', u'O'), (u',', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'reports', u'O'), (u'sales', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'61.91', u'O'), (u'million', u'O'), (u'NES', u'O'), (u'hardware', u'O'), (u'units', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'500.01', u'O'), (u'million', u'O'), (u'NES', u'O'), (u'software', u'O'), (u'units', u'O'), (u'worldwide.', u'O')][(u'The', u'O'), (u'Super', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Entertainment', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'System', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'(abbreviated', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Super', u'O'), (u'NES', u'O'), (u'or', u'O'), (u'SNES)', u'O'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'16-bit', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'console,', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'North', u'LOCATION'), (u'America', u'LOCATION'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'1991,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Europe', u'LOCATION'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'1992.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'initially', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Japan', u'LOCATION'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'1990', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Super', u'O'), (u'Famicom,', u'O'), (u'officially', u'O'), (u'adopting', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'colloquially', u'O'), (u'abbreviated', u'O'), (u'name', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'predecessor.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'introduced', u'O'), (u'advanced', u'O'), (u'graphics', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'sound', u'O'), (u'capabilities', u'O'), (u'compared', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'other', u'O'), (u'consoles', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'time.', u'O'), (u'Soon,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'development', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'variety', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'enhancement', u'O'), (u'chips', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'were', u'O'), (u'integrated', u'O'), (u'onto', u'O'), (u'each', u'O'), (u'new', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u"cartridge's", u'O'), (u'circuit', u'O'), (u'boards,', u'O'), (u'progressed', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u"SNES's", u'O'), (u'competitive', u'O'), (u'edge.', u'O'), (u'While', u'O'), (u'even', u'O'), (u'crude', u'O'), (u'three-dimensional', u'O'), (u'graphics', u'O'), (u'had', u'O'), (u'previously', u'O'), (u'rarely', u'O'), (u'been', u'O'), (u'seen', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'home', u'O'), (u'consoles,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Super', u'O'), (u"NES's", u'O'), (u'enhancement', u'O'), (u'chips', u'O'), (u'suddenly', u'O'), (u'enabled', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'new', u'O'), (u'caliber', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'containing', u'O'), (u'increasingly', u'O'), (u'sophisticated', u'O'), (u'faux', u'O'), (u'3D', u'O'), (u'effects', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'seen', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u"1991's", u'O'), (u'"Pilotwings"', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u"1992's", u'O'), (u'"Super', u'O'), (u'Mario', u'PERSON'), (u'Kart".', u'O'), (u'Argonaut', u'O'), (u'Games', u'O'), (u'developed', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Super', u'O'), (u'FX', u'O'), (u'chip', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'order', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'replicate', u'O'), (u'3D', u'O'), (u'graphics', u'O'), (u'from', u'O'), (u'their', u'O'), (u'earlier', u'O'), (u'Atari', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'ST', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Amiga', u'O'), (u'"Starglider"', u'O'), (u'series', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Super', u'O'), (u'NES', u'O'), (u'(more', u'O'), (u'specifically,', u'O'), (u'"Starglider', u'O'), (u'2"),', u'O'), (u'starting', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'"Star', u'O'), (u'Fox"', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'1993.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'SNES', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'best-selling', u'O'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'16-bit', u'O'), (u'era', u'O'), (u'although', u'O'), (u'having', u'O'), (u'experienced', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'relatively', u'O'), (u'late', u'O'), (u'start', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'fierce', u'O'), (u'competition', u'O'), (u'from', u'O'), (u"Sega's", u'O'), (u'Mega', u'O'), (u'DriveGenesis', u'O'), (u'console.', u'O'), (u',', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'reports', u'O'), (u'sales', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'49.10', u'O'), (u'million', u'O'), (u'SNES', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'hardware', u'O'), (u'units', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'379.06', u'O'), (u'million', u'O'), (u'SNES', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'software', u'O'), (u'units', u'O'), (u'worldwide.', u'O')][(u'The', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'64', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'1996,', u'O'), (u'featuring', u'O'), (u'3D', u'O'), (u'polygon', u'O'), (u'model', u'O'), (u'rendering', u'O'), (u'capabilities', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'built-in', u'O'), (u'multiplayer', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'up', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'four', u'O'), (u'players.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u"system's", u'O'), (u'controller', u'O'), (u'introduced', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'analog', u'O'), (u'stick', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'later', u'O'), (u'introduced', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Rumble', u'O'), (u'Pak,', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'accessory', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'controller', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'produces', u'O'), (u'force', u'O'), (u'feedback', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'compatible', u'O'), (u'games.', u'O'), (u'Both', u'O'), (u'are', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'first', u'O'), (u'such', u'O'), (u'features', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'have', u'O'), (u'come', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'market', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'home', u'O'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'gaming', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'eventually', u'O'), (u'became', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'"de', u'O'), (u'facto"', u'O'), (u'industry', u'O'), (u'standard.', u'O'), (u'Announced', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'1995,', u'O'), (u'prior', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u"console's", u'O'), (u'1996', u'O'), (u'launch,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'64DD', u'O'), (u'("DD"', u'O'), (u'standing', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'"Disk', u'O'), (u'Drive")', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'designed', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'enable', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'development', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'new', u'O'), (u'genre', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'way', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'64', u'O'), (u'MB', u'O'), (u'writable', u'O'), (u'magnetic', u'O'), (u'disks,', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'editing,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Internet', u'O'), (u'connectivity.', u'O'), (u'Eventually', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'only', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Japan', u'LOCATION'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'1999,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'64DD', u'O'), (u"peripheral's", u'O'), (u'commercial', u'O'), (u'failure', u'O'), (u'there', u'O'), (u'resulted', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'only', u'O'), (u'nine', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'being', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'precluded', u'O'), (u'further', u'O'), (u'worldwide', u'O')][(u'The', u'O'), (u'GameCube', u'O'), (u'(officially', u'O'), (u'called', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'GameCube,', u'O'), (u'abbreviated', u'O'), (u'NGC', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Japan', u'LOCATION'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'GCN', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'North', u'LOCATION'), (u'America)', u'LOCATION'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'2001,', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Japan', u'LOCATION'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'North', u'PERSON'), (u'America,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'2002', u'O'), (u'worldwide.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'sixth-generation', u'O'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'successor', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'64', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'competed', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u"Sony's", u'O'), (u'PlayStation', u'O'), (u'2,', u'O'), (u"Microsoft's", u'O'), (u'Xbox,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u"Sega's", u'O'), (u'Dreamcast.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'GameCube', u'O'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'first', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'use', u'O'), (u'optical', u'O'), (u'discs', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'primary', u'O'), (u'storage', u'O'), (u'medium.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'discs', u'O'), (u'are', u'O'), (u'similar', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'miniDVD', u'O'), (u'format,', u'O'), (u'but', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'system', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'not', u'O'), (u'designed', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'play', u'O'), (u'standard', u'O'), (u'DVDs', u'O'), (u'or', u'O'), (u'audio', u'O'), (u'CDs.', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'introduced', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'variety', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'connectivity', u'O'), (u'options', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'GameCube.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u"GameCube's", u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'library', u'O'), (u'has', u'O'), (u'sparse', u'O'), (u'support', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Internet', u'O'), (u'gaming,', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'feature', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'requires', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'use', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'aftermarket', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'GameCube', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Broadband', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Adapter', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'and', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Modem', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Adapter.', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'GameCube', u'O'), (u'supports', u'O'), (u'connectivity', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Game', u'O'), (u'Boy', u'O'), (u'Advance,', u'O'), (u'allowing', u'O'), (u'players', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'access', u'O'), (u'exclusive', u'O'), (u'in-game', u'O'), (u'features', u'O'), (u'using', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'handheld', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'second', u'O'), (u'screen', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'controller.', u'O'), (u',', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'reports', u'O'), (u'sales', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'21.74', u'O'), (u'million', u'O'), (u'GameCube', u'O'), (u'hardware', u'O'), (u'units', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'208.57', u'O'), (u'million', u'O'), (u'GameCube', u'O'), (u'software', u'O'), (u'units', u'O'), (u'worldwide.', u'O')][(u'The', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'during', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'holiday', u'O'), (u'season', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'2006', u'O'), (u'worldwide.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'system', u'O'), (u'features', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'Remote', u'O'), (u'controller,', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'can', u'O'), (u'be', u'O'), (u'used', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'handheld', u'O'), (u'pointing', u'O'), (u'device', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'detects', u'O'), (u'movement', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'three', u'O'), (u'dimensions.', u'O'), (u'Another', u'O'), (u'notable', u'O'), (u'feature', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'WiiConnect24,', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'enables', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'receive', u'O'), (u'messages', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'updates', u'O'), (u'over', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Internet', u'O'), (u'while', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'standby', u'O'), (u'mode.', u'O'), (u'It', u'O'), (u'also', u'O'), (u'features', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'download', u'O'), (u'service,', u'O'), (u'called', u'O'), (u'"Virtual', u'O'), (u'Console",', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'features', u'O'), (u'emulated', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'from', u'O'), (u'past', u'O'), (u'systems.', u'O'), (u'Since', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'release,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'has', u'O'), (u'spawned', u'O'), (u'many', u'O'), (u'peripheral', u'O'), (u'devices,', u'O'), (u'including', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Balance', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Board', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'and', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Motion', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Plus,', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'has', u'O'), (u'had', u'O'), (u'several', u'O'), (u'hardware', u'O'), (u'revisions.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'"Wii', u'O'), (u'Family', u'O'), (u'Edition"', u'O'), (u'variant', u'O'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'identical', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'original', u'O'), (u'model,', u'O'), (u'but', u'O'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'designed', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'sit', u'O'), (u'horizontally', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'removes', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'GameCube', u'O'), (u'compatibility.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'"Wii', u'O'), (u'Mini"', u'O'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'smaller,', u'O'), (u'redesigned', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'lacks', u'O'), (u'GameCube', u'O'), (u'compatibility,', u'O'), (u'online', u'O'), (u'connectivity,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'SD', u'O'), (u'card', u'O'), (u'slot', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Wi-Fi', u'O'), (u'support,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'has', u'O'), (u'only', u'O'), (u'one', u'O'), (u'USB', u'O'), (u'port', u'O'), (u'unlike', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'previous', u'O'), (u"models'", u'O'), (u'two.', u'O'), (u',', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'reports', u'O'), (u'sales', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'101.63', u'O'), (u'million', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'hardware', u'O'), (u'units', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'914.28', u'O'), (u'million', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'software', u'O'), (u'units', u'O'), (u'worldwide,', u'O'), (u'making', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u"Nintendo's", u'O'), (u'best-selling', u'O'), (u'home', u'O'), (u'video', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'console.', u'O')][(u'The', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'U,', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'successor', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Wii,', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'during', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'holiday', u'O'), (u'season', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'2012', u'O'), (u'worldwide.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'U', u'O'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'first', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'support', u'O'), (u'high-definition', u'O'), (u'graphics.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u"U's", u'O'), (u'primary', u'O'), (u'controller', u'O'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'U', u'O'), (u'GamePad,', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'features', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'embedded', u'O'), (u'touchscreen.', u'O'), (u'Each', u'O'), (u'software', u'O'), (u'title', u'O'), (u'may', u'O'), (u'be', u'O'), (u'designed', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'utilize', u'O'), (u'this', u'O'), (u'touchscreen', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'being', u'O'), (u'supplemental', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'main', u'O'), (u'TV,', u'O'), (u'or', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'only', u'O'), (u'screen', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Off-TV', u'O'), (u'Play.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'system', u'O'), (u'supports', u'O'), (u'most', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'controllers', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'accessories,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'more', u'O'), (u'classically', u'O'), (u'shaped', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'U', u'O'), (u'Pro', u'O'), (u'Controller.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'system', u'O'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'backward', u'O'), (u'compatible', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'software', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'accessories;', u'O'), (u'this', u'O'), (u'mode', u'O'), (u'also', u'O'), (u'utilizes', u'O'), (u'Wii-based', u'O'), (u'controllers,', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'optionally', u'O'), (u'offers', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'GamePad', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'primary', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'display', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'motion', u'O'), (u'sensor', u'O'), (u'bar.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'has', u'O'), (u'various', u'O'), (u'online', u'O'), (u'services', u'O'), (u'powered', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Network,', u'O'), (u'including:', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'eShop', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'online', u'O'), (u'distribution', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'software', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'content;', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Miiverse,', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'social', u'O'), (u'network', u'O'), (u'which', u'O'), (u'can', u'O'), (u'be', u'O'), (u'variously', u'O'), (u'integrated', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'applications.', u'O'), (u'As', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'31', u'O'), (u'March', u'O'), (u'2016,', u'O'), (u'worldwide', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'U', u'O'), (u'sales', u'O'), (u'had', u'O'), (u'totaled', u'O'), (u'12.80', u'O'), (u'million', u'O'), (u'hardware', u'O'), (u'units', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'84.04', u'O'), (u'million', u'O'), (u'software', u'O'), (u'units.', u'O')][(u'On', u'O'), (u'17', u'O'), (u'March', u'O'), (u'2015,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'announced', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'new', u'O'), (u'"dedicated', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'platform', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'brand', u'O'), (u'new', u'O'), (u'concept"', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'codename', u'O'), (u'"NX"', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'would', u'O'), (u'be', u'O'), (u'further', u'O'), (u'revealed', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'2016.', u'O'), (u'Reggie', u'PERSON'), (u'Fils-Aim\xe9,', u'O'), (u'president', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'America,', u'O'), (u'referred', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'NX', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'"our', u'O'), (u'next', u'O'), (u'home', u'O'), (u'console"', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'June', u'O'), (u'2015', u'O'), (u'interview', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'"The', u'O'), (u'Wall', u'O'), (u'Street', u'O'), (u'Journal".', u'O'), (u'In', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'later', u'O'), (u'article', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'16', u'O'), (u'October', u'O'), (u'2015,', u'O'), (u'"The', u'O'), (u'Wall', u'O'), (u'Street', u'O'), (u'Journal"', u'O'), (u'relayed', u'O'), (u'speculation', u'O'), (u'from', u'O'), (u'unnamed', u'O'), (u'inside', u'O'), (u'sources', u'O'), (u'that,', u'O'), (u'although', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'NX', u'O'), (u'hardware', u'O'), (u'specifications', u'O'), (u'were', u'O'), (u'unknown,', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'may', u'O'), (u'be', u'O'), (u'intended', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'feature', u'O'), (u'"industry', u'O'), (u'leading"', u'O'), (u'hardware', u'O'), (u'specifications', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'include', u'O'), (u'both', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'mobile', u'O'), (u'unit', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'could', u'O'), (u'either', u'O'), (u'be', u'O'), (u'used', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'or', u'O'), (u'taken', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'road', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'separate', u'O'), (u'use.', u'O'), (u'It', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'also', u'O'), (u'reported', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'had', u'O'), (u'begun', u'O'), (u'distributing', u'O'), (u'software', u'O'), (u'development', u'O'), (u'kits', u'O'), (u'(SDKs)', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'NX', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'third-party', u'O'), (u'developers,', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'unnamed', u'O'), (u'source', u'O'), (u'further', u'O'), (u'speculating', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'these', u'O'), (u'moves', u'O'), (u'"[suggest', u'O'), (u'that]', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'company', u'O'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'track', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'introduce', u'O'), (u'[NX]', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'early', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'[2016]."', u'O'), (u'At', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u"investor's", u'O'), (u'meeting', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'27', u'O'), (u'April', u'O'), (u'2016,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'announced', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'NX', u'O'), (u'would', u'O'), (u'be', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'worldwide', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'March', u'O'), (u'2017.', u'O'), (u'In', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'interview', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'Asahi', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Shimbun', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'May', u'O'), (u'2016,', u'O'), (u'Kimishima', u'PERSON'), (u'referred', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'NX', u'LOCATION'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'"neither', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'successor', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'U', u'O'), (u'nor', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'3DS",', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'well', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'being', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'"new', u'O'), (u'way', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'playing', u'O'), (u'games,"', u'O'), (u'but', u'O'), (u'it', u'O'), (u'would', u'O'), (u'"slow', u'O'), (u'Wii', u'O'), (u'U', u'O'), (u'sales"', u'O'), (u'upon', u'O'), (u'reveal', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'dissemination.', u'O'), (u'In', u'O'), (u'June', u'O'), (u'2016,', u'O'), (u'Miyamoto', u'PERSON'), (u'stated', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'reason', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'had', u'O'), (u'not', u'O'), (u'released', u'O'), (u'any', u'O'), (u'information', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'"NX"', u'O'), (u'up', u'O'), (u'until', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'point', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'because', u'O'), (u'they', u'O'), (u'were', u'O'), (u'afraid', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'imitators,', u'O'), (u'saying', u'O'), (u'he', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'thought', u'O'), (u'other', u'O'), (u'companies', u'O'), (u'could', u'O'), (u'copy', u'O'), (u'"an', u'O'), (u'idea', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u"[they're]", u'O'), (u'working', u'O'), (u'on."', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'same', u'O'), (u'day,', u'O'), (u'Kimishima', u'PERSON'), (u'revealed', u'O'), (u'during', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Q&A', u'O'), (u'session', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'investors', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'they', u'O'), (u'were', u'O'), (u'also', u'O'), (u'researching', u'O'), (u'virtual', u'O'), (u'reality.', u'O'), (u'On', u'O'), (u'19', u'O'), (u'October', u'O'), (u'2016,', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'announced', u'O'), (u'they', u'O'), (u'would', u'O'), (u'release', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'trailer', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'console', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'following', u'O'), (u'day.', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'next', u'O'), (u'day', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'unveiled', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'trailer', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Switch.', u'O')][(u'Game', u'O'), (u'&', u'O'), (u'Watch', u'O'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'line', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'handheld', u'O'), (u'electronic', u'O'), (u'games', u'O'), (u'produced', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'from', u'O'), (u'1980', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'1991.', u'O'), (u'Created', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'designer', u'O'), (u'Gunpei', u'PERSON'), (u'Yokoi,', u'O'), (u'each', u'O'), (u'"Game', u'O'), (u'&', u'O'), (u'Watch"', u'O'), (u'features', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'single', u'O'), (u'game', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'be', u'O'), (u'played', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'LCD', u'O'), (u'screen', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'addition', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'clock,', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'alarm,', u'O'), (u'or', u'O'), (u'both.', u'O'), (u'It', u'O'), (u'was', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'earliest', u'O'), (u'Nintendo', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'product', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'garner', u'O'), (u'major', u'O'), (u'success.', u'O')][(u'After', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'success', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'"Game', u'O'), (u'&', u'O'), (u'Watch"', u'O'), (u'series,', u'O'), (u'Yokoi', u'PERSON'), (u'developed', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Game', u'O'), (u'Boy', u'O'), (u'handheld', u'O'), (u'console,